Get out of my house.
Hey, what happened?   Are you
seeing brother how my family is treating me
?
What happened?
What did these people not do to us?  These
people had to listen to bhajans early in the morning.
Yes.
Brought home theatre.
Good.   There was
no iron in the house.
Brought the iron.
very nice.
Mom was having difficulty grinding the spices.
Yes.
Brought the mixer.
very nice.
You stole everything and brought it here.
[laughs]
If you have such a problem with money, then there is
an app in the Play Store, Son.
Earn money by playing games there.
How brother?  Look,
here if you play any game for 20 minutes then
you will get 26 gems which is equal to ₹12.
Play games comfortably,
collect money, make bank transfers.
More than money in your bank account the link to this app is
in my bio.  Quickly
go there and download and sign up.
You will get ₹7 instant signup bonus.
Hey, thank you so much brother.  very nice man.
Very good.  Okay 1 minute 1 minute 1 minute I'm coming
one minute.
What happened?
Brother, this Ernawa stole your house in front of you.
[screaming]
[laughter]